let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the initial focus of the HTML and CSS series?",
    answer: "Building a responsive website",
    options: [
      "Building a responsive website",
      "Learning advanced web development concepts",
      "Exploring front-end, back-end, and full-stack development",
      "Installing code editor extensions"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the estimated timeframe to learn HTML and CSS with consistent study and coding?",
    answer: "1 month to 1.5 months",
    options: [
      "1 month to 1.5 months",
      "3 months",
      "6 months",
      "1 year"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which essential skills are listed for front-end developers?",
    answer: "HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Git",
    options: [
      "HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP",
      "HTML, CSS, Python, and Ruby",
      "HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Git",
      "Java, CSS, JavaScript, and C++"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How does the browser render the HTML document?",
    answer: "By constructing a Document Object Model",
    options: [
      "By sending separate HTTP requests",
      "By constructing a Document Object Model",
      "By using an external web server",
      "By displaying the page immediately"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does HTML5 introduce for doctype declaration?",
    answer: "'doctype html'",
    options: [
      "'Doctype.HTML'",
      "'Doctype <!HTML>'",
      "'doctype html'",
      "'Doctype Website'"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the purpose of the alt attribute in HTML images?",
    answer: "Provides a description for the image",
    options: [
      "Provides a caption for the image",
      "Defines image height and width",
      "Provides a description for the image",
      "Specifies the image format"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which element is used to represent strong importance in HTML content?",
    answer: "strong",
    options: [
      "b",
      "strong",
      "em",
      "i"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What does the i element represent in HTML content?",
    answer: "Italic content",
    options: [
      "Italic content",
      "Bold content",
      "Underlined content",
      "Important content"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which HTML element is used for creating a hyperlink?",
    answer: "anchor",
    options: [
      "anchor",
      "link",
      "href",
      "navigate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What does an anchor element do in HTML?",
    answer: "a hyperlink to another webpage",
    options: [
      "Creates inline images",
      "Defines the website's main content",
      "Specifies the image format",
      "a hyperlink to another webpage"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "How do you create a link to jump to the top of the page within the same webpage in HTML?",
    answer: "Using empty fragment",
    options: [
      "Using absolute URL",
      "Using empty fragment",
      "Using relative URL",
      "Using hash symbol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is the purpose of using object fit property in CSS?",
    answer: "Resize to fit the container",
    options: [
      "Adjust the image's brightness",
      "Resize to fit the container",
      "Apply a color overlay to the image",
      "Add a border around the image"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which CSS property is used to set the border radius for an image?",
    answer: "border-radius",
    options: [
      "image-radius",
      "border-radius",
      "round-image",
      "image-border"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What is the function of the float property in CSS?",
    answer: "Push the element to the right",
    options: [
      "Rotate the element",
      "Push the element to the right",
      "Transition the element's position",
      "Slightly move the element"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "How can HTML entities be used to display special characters?",
    answer: "Start with an ampersand and end with a semicolon",
    options: [
      "Enclose special characters in curly braces",
      "Enclose special characters in square brackets",
      "Start with an ampersand and end with a semicolon",
      "Start with a pound sign and end with an exclamation mark"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "What is the role of the 'head' section in an HTML document?",
    answer: "Contains metadata and links to external resources",
    options: [
      "Defines the main content of the page",
      "Provides a space for adding images",
      "Contains metadata and links to external resources",
      "Specifies the structure of the web page"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which tool is used for launching on a development web server?",
    answer: "Live server extension",
    options: [
      "VS Code",
      "Prettier Code Formatter",
      "Live server extension",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Prettier' plugin in VS Code?",
    answer: "Formatting HTML and CSS code",
    options: [
      "Analyzing website performance metrics",
      "Formatting HTML and CSS code",
      "Creating responsive web designs",
      "Writing JavaScript algorithms"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Which attribute provides a description for an image when it cannot be loaded?",
    answer: "alt",
    options: [
      "title",
      "alt",
      "src",
      "description"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "What do front-end developers need to learn as essential skills mentioned in job descriptions?",
    answer: "HTML, CSS, and JavaScript",
    options: [
      "HTML, CSS, and JavaScript",
      "Python, PHP, and Java",
      "Ruby, C++, and Swift",
      "MySQL, MongoDB, and Django"
    ]
  }
];
